
  [
    {
      "tutorial": [["Welcome to the Boolean World!\n\n You are going to rescue your friend from a planet that is going to explode soon. You have to get to the Planet in time to rescue your friend. First you need to collect the required essentials to survive in space."],
        ["Boolean Algebra is used in Computer Programing and Digital Electronics. It is used to represent things as either true or false. \n 0 = false  \n 1 = true\nExample:\nYou go to school on weekdays only.\nToday is Monday = true, you are at school.\nToday is Sunday = false, you are not at school"],
        ["NOT\nYou can also use a NOT to make a statement that is \ntrue to false \nfalse to true\nFor example. The lights are NOT off  = the lights are on\n"],
        ["OR\nOR statements make things true if one or all conditions are true.\nIf none of the conditions are true then the statement is false.\n For Example: \n Today is sunny = true you will play outside.\n Today is rainy = False you will not play outisde\n Today is Cloudy = true you will play outside."],
        ["AND\nYou can check more than one condition by using an AND.\nWith an AND both conditions must be true to = true\nIf only one condition is true then the whole thing is false.\n For Example: You play outside after school AND sunny days.\n  It is after school and it is raining = FALSE you will not be playing since it is Not sunny\n Example: It is during school and it is sunny = FALSE you will not be playing out side since it is NOT after school "]
      ],
      "optionNum": 0
    },
    {
     "question": "Going on the space adventure requires that your spaceship is working.\n After an inspection of the ship you find that you ship’s rockets are not working.\nWill you be able to go on the space adventure?",
     "optionNum": 2,
     "option1": "Yes",
     "option2": "No",
     "answer": "No"
    },
    {
      "question": "You fix your spaceship and are ready to go. \nYou plot a course to your destination and are ready to make to the jump to hyperspace. \nBefore you can go, the course must NOT have any obstacles in the way. \nYou review the course and find that it is free of obstacles.\n Can you make the jump to hyperspace?",
      "optionNum": 2,
      "option1": "Yes",
      "option2": "No",
      "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
      "question": "You make the jump, arrive at the planet, and are ready to land. To land, the spaceship must NOT be going too fast. The speed indicator shows that the ship is in the correct speed range. Are you ready to land?",
      "optionNum": 2,
      "option1": "Yes",
      "option2": "No",
      "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
      "question": "Your first mission is to explore planet landmarks. You are required to explore a mountain OR valley. You look around and decide to explore a cave. Have you satisfied the mission objective?",
      "optionNum": 2,
      "option1": "Yes",
      "option2": "No",
      "answer": "No"
    },
    {
      "question": "After exploring a nearby mountain, the next objective is gather samples from the planet. You can gather either rock OR dirt samples to complete this objective",
      "optionNum": 3,
      "option1": "Rock",
      "option2": "Liquid",
      "option3": "Dirt",
      "answer": "OR",
      "answer1": "Rock",
      "answer2": "Dirt"
    },
    {
      "question": "You need to gather more information about the planet. You can measure the planet’s temperature OR atmosphere in order to satisfy the mission objective.",
      "optionNum": 3,
      "option1": "Temperature",
      "option2": "Atmosphere",
      "option3": "Moons",
      "answer": "OR",
      "answer1": "Temperature",
      "answer2": "Atmosphere"

    },
    {
      "question": "In order to travel to the next planet, you need to plot a course for the new planet AND ensure you spaceship engines are working properly. You plot a course in the ship’s computer but forget to check the the ship’s engines. Are you ready to move on to the next planet?",
      "optionNum": 2,
      "option1": "Yes",
      "option2": "No",
      "answer": "No"
    },
    {
      "question": "Your ship also needs to refill life support supplies. You need air AND water to continue on your adventure. Gather the necessary supplies",
      "optionNum": 3,
      "option1": "Air",
      "option2": "Dirt",
      "option3": "Water",
      "answer": "AND",
      "answer1": "Air",
      "answer2": "Water"
    },
    {
      "question": "Finally, the spaceship needs more Purple fuel crystals. In order to make more you need both Red AND Blue crystals. Choose the correct crystal pair to make your ship go.",
      "optionNum": 4,
      "option1": "Green",
      "option2": "Red",
      "option3": "Blue",
      "option4": "Yellow",
      "answer": "AND",
      "answer1": "Red",
      "answer2": "Blue"
    },
    {
      "question": "Congratulations you have completed the boolean algebra world!",
      "optionNum": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Wrong: Try agian",
      "optionNum": 0
    }

  ]
